

WEI-RU TAI

UI UX Designer



CONTACT



wei-ru.tai@uni-weimar.de



+49 176 89097796



Carl-F-Streichhan str. 4a 99425 Weimar



www.behance.net/weirutai

SKILLS

- Interface Design (ios/android)
- Interaction Design
- User Experience Research
- Graphic + Icon Design
- Adobe CC + figma + sketch

LANGUAGES

Native Speaker

MANDARIN (CHINESE) TAIWANESE Native Speaker Proficient User C1 ENGLISH GERMAN Intermediate B2

My name is Weiru, Tai. I am a media art and design student who has experience working as an UX/UI Designer in app development from initial planning, implementation of wireframe, design proposal, device version design to product launch.

I am familiar with the tools of Graphic design, Interface design, Wireframe, Prototype, Data and specifications clarification and always enjoying myself very much creating innovative digital products.



EDUCATION

Bauhaus-Universität Weimar

Media art and design Master's degree Interface Design 2019-current

Yuan-Ze University 1,28 (GPA: 3,72/4) College of Informatics B.A. Information Communication

2010-2014



AWARDS

2014

K.T.Creativity Award-Gold Award

> Asia Digital Art Award-Finalist Prize

Department of Cultural Affairs Taipei City Government-Highest Budget Supplement



EXPERIENCE

March 2018-O PROJECT MANAGER A u g u s t 2 0 1 8

March2017- O UI UX Designer

Hualien City, Taiwan

Dahan Institute of Technology

February 2018

Hello Media Taipei City, Taiwan

July2015-February 2017

ART TEACHER/ AUPAIR/ CHINESE TEACHER Working Holiday

March 2015-

ART TEACHER June2015

Taipei American School Taipei City, Taiwan

London, United Kingdom

March 2013 -May2014

UI DESIGNER INTERN

Mobius Design Taipei City, Taiwan

March 2012-June 2014

SCHOOL EVENT HOST Yuan Ze University
FOR INTERNATIONAL STUDENTS

Volunteer Job, Taiwan